searchenginegenie.com 2018-09-25

# Privacy policy search engine optimization SEO marketing search engine genie

**Search Engine Genie** has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy and protection of your information. As part of the normal operation of services, we collect and, in some instances, disclose information about you. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

1\. Information Collected During Your Use of the **Search Engine Genie** Service 

In order to register, users are required to give us contact information (e.g., your name and email address), unique identifiers (e.g., your password), and demographic information (e.g., your zip code). Certain information, such as passwords and email addresses, is collected in order to verify your identity and for use in our records.

If you decide to purchase any **Search Engine Genie** Solutions, **Search Engine Genie** will need to collect certain financial information, such as your credit card number, credit card expiration date, and billing address ("Financial Information"). Financial Information that is collected is used to check your qualifications for registration, to bill you for products and services, and for other purposes. Search Engine Genie does not share Financial Information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide you with Search Engine Genie Solutions.

2\. Our Use of Your Information 

We use customer contact information from the registration form to send you information about **Search Engine Genie** and promotional material from some of our partners. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. We may use your IP address to help protect our partners and us from fraud.

We may use demographic and profile data to tailor your experience on our service, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying the content according to your preferences.

3\. Our Disclosure of Your Information 

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described in this Privacy Policy and our Member Agreement without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. We may also offer you the option to attract visitors to your site through participation in search engines, comparative shopping services, or similar distribution opportunities.

**Search Engine Genie** will never willfully sell, lease, or rent any of your or your business' personally identifiable information to any third party without first receiving your permission.

**Search Engine Genie** offers features and services on our site where we will need to provide some of the information publicly available on your Member Site to third-party search engines offering search services. Should you choose to use any of these features and services, we may do the following with such information: distribute member product and service information and information about your store, your products and services, your web site address (URL), your contact information, and other information, to such search engines and various other comparative shopping and search services; and create a database of publicly available information about you or your business to its search partners with the express purpose of driving Internet user traffic to Member Sites, provided that such information is useful to the end users of the Member Sites. Publicly available information means information available to the public on your web site, and may include the following: information about the products or services you offer through the Member Site, your operating hours, your business address, your URL, your business contact information, and other such information. In no event, however, will we disclose any of your Financial Information.

**Search Engine Genie** cannot ensure that all of your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not described in this Privacy Policy. For instance, we may be required to disclose personally identifiable information to the government or by court order under certain circumstances, or other situations that may require such disclosure. In addition, you authorize us to disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. This site contains links to other sites. **Search Engine Genie** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

4\. Security 

In order to maximize the protection of your information, **Search Engine Genie** Service uses state-of-the-art technology to protect your data from use, misuse, or alteration by unauthorized third parties. Currently, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your data and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all your personal information, including your credit card number, name, and address, as it is transmitted over the Internet. Of course, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be one hundred percent secure, and **Search Engine Genie** does not warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data on or through the use of the **Search Engine Genie** Service is at your own risk.

5\. General 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the **Search Engine Genie** Member Agreement.

6\. Cookie Usage and EU cookie concent policy: 

Search Engine Genie may sometimes use cookies to personalize your experience. Cookies are used to recognize you through your web browser. You have the right to accept or reject a cookie. This option is available in all browsers.  

Search engine genie serves third party advertisements like Google adsense to serve ads. Google adsense uses cookies to serve best and relevant ads to you. Google uses DART cookie which will serve personalized ads. Google also serves ads based on your interests and searches online by using a cookie. 

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions should not cause a problem with our site. 

European union cookie consent policy:  

Search Engine Genie complies with EU cookie consent policy. 

For more information on Search Engine Genie’s services, contact us at ****[webpromotions@gmail.com](mailto:webpromotions@gmail.com)****
